I always believe that I can't share my sadness.
You must have seen my videos, they are fun,
entertaining, humorous.
And my videos always start with a smile.
But in today's video, I have something that
I can't tell you with a smile.
You must have seen the title and thumbnail.
And if you are watching this video, then definitely I am alive.
Now you must be thinking that what is so big that
I am talking about living and dying.
Look, this is not a recent news, this is 5 months old.
And seriously, after seeing the title and thumbnail,
Many of you will say that I met you,
I was with you, still you didn't share.
Then definitely my answer is that I don't feel like sharing sadness.
Very rarely, very limited and closed
people know about this thing.
And maybe I am not even making this video,
But there are some things with me that I want to share.
And obviously, if it benefits people,
Then what is better than that.
So let me tell you a little back story.
On 7th August, we purchased Mahindra XUV900
and posted it on social media.
People congratulated us a lot.
And as a boy, you will be able to relate that
a car is a special purchase for a boy.
Of course, it is for everyone, but specifically for boys,
They have a different love for cars.
Whether they buy it or not, a friend buys a car or whatever,
Their happiness is at a different level.
On top of that, it is such an expensive purchase.
And the reason why we chose XEV-9E
was that it is a tech-loaded car.
Secondly, it is an EV because I already had a fuel car.
So I thought it will contribute towards the environment.
Then we posted a review of it and got a lot of love.
In that, I covered all its tech features.
And I still get comments in that video
that how detailed that video was.
Whereas, it was my first car review.
And I used this car as much as I showed in that video.
Because when this car came, initially there were
small issues in it, which I shared on Twitter.
Some limited people had seen that tweet as well.
There were some body paint issues, pen marks on the seat,
and other small technical issues.
Then they got sorted and they
asked me to remove the tweet.
I thought it was not a big issue, so I removed it.
This went on for 3-4 days.
Then the tech review that I was telling you about,
it went on for 7 days.
And then I gave this car for PPF,
in that as well, 4-5 days passed on.
And in total, I haven't even drove
this car for around 100 KMs.
And the evening when I got my car back after PPF,
I felt that it has been a long time so let's travel with it.
Me and my friend went to Maggi point,
Those who have been to Dehradun-Masuri will know
that there are many Maggi points on the way.
We ate something there, and we were just
coming back through Old Masuri Road.
And there is a sharp U-shaped turn,
from where a car was coming from the wrong side.
I steered a little to the left,
And the car went straight into the Gorge.
And the first credit goes to the durability of the car.
After such a big accident, I didn't even get a scratch.
This happened on 29th August, and from that day till today,
I am active on social media, gaming channel,
And I am making content for my tech channel as well.
I didn't even get a scratch on my head
despite having a glass moonroof.
All the airbags were open,
And when this happened, I was in shock.
Because when the accident happened,
I didn't realize one thing.
But after some seconds,
I realized that the car is upside down.
Thank God, the side on which the car fell,
there was water just next to it,
And it could have gone into the water as well.
The biggest thing is that it was an EV vehicle,
and we could have got an electric shock as well.
And we don't even know how deep the water was,
so things could have been worse for us.
But I thank God that I was saved,
And there would be your blessings as well.
So that I am sitting in front of you even
after such a major crash
And there was a feature of the car,
Emergency call was made automatically through the car,
I talked on the call
And they took our location and sent the police there.
The police also came immediately.
Now, who is at fault here?
First, the one who was coming on the wrong side.
Other than that, big thanks to the police and the
locals who helped in rescuing us and the car.
Because the Gorge was very deep,
And it seemed impossible for us to come up from there.
And the government infrastructure is also very poor.
Because that U-shaped turn, I will show you the
Google map image, you can see how sharp it is.
And you must have seen in the hilly areas,
there are barricades of metal or concrete.
And when the accident happened, do you know
what the locals were saying while rescuing us?
That this happens here almost everyday.
And after that, I took some photos.
In this specific portion,
There were no barricades from where my car fell.
If this barricade had been there,
Then my car would have just got stuck there and
there wouldn't have been such a big accident.
And the most surprising thing is that after 3-4 days,
I went to the insurance officer to show him the location
when he had to do the inspection.
If you compare my 3-4 days old photo,
there are barricades ahead.
But that day, 2-3 barricades ahead were also missing.
That is, there have been accidents
even after my accident.
Look, even after so many accidents,
The government is not taking any action there.
And this is just an example.
There are millions of such examples where
people lose their lives just because of infrastructure.
You must be aware of the case of Noida,
which happened recently.
A boy drowned and died.
Now, after all this, comes the insurance company.
Now, when we came out of there,
I called the insurance company first.
That we need roadside assistance.
We have to get the car out.
They directly refused that if the car has gone into
the gorge, then we will not be able to help.
We only provide roadside assistance.
I also did some research about this.
Yes, insurance companies do not provide cranes etc.
But it was night time, at least they could have helped.
But they didn't even ask anything like that.
They just refused that we don't have service.
And big thanks to that police officer who was standing with us.
He gave us the number of the crane operator.
And the crane operator asked us for Rs 20,000 to come there.
Now, I have Rs 20,000.
If there is a person who doesn't have the money on the
spot at that time in such a situation.
Neither cash nor in bank account.
He will have a lot of problems.
And the best part, that police officer said,
Until the crane does not come, I am standing here with you.
Then we told him that no sir, you can go.
We will do it.
And it took 3-4 hours for the crane to reach the location.
And obviously, I couldn't leave my car and go there.
That I will see it tomorrow.
This is India, There would be nothing by the morning.
Then the crane came.
We took the car out of the crane.
And we took it to Mahindra's workshop in a tow truck.
And this was the same truck that ICICI Lombard sent.
Now, after such a big accident, after such a condition of the car.
As a boy or as a new car owner.
He will think that I will not drive this car.
First of all, such a big incident has happened to you through the same car.
And secondly, superstition sits in the mind.
So we thought that our car should go for total loss.
Total loss is a situation in which there are
a lot of expenses in the car.
Specifically, if the cost is coming around
70-75% of insured declared value.
Then the company does not repair it.
It declares it in total loss.
And we get a return to invoice.
That is, whatever we have spent.
Whatever on-road cost we have incurred.
We get all that back.
And after that, we can buy a new car.
After that, the car was surveyed in Mahindra.
And they made a quotation of Rs 56 lakhs.
Now you will say, how the quotation is so high?
On-road the car costs Rs 33 lakhs.
Basically, whenever you look at the assembled parts.
For example, you bought an iPhone worth Rs 1 lakh.
If you see the board, Camera, Battery, Body,
Screen of a Rs 1,00,000 iPhone.
If you look at everything separately.
Then its value will be more than Rs 1 lakh.
So this happens in cars.
When quotations of different parts are seen.
In that, GST, Labour cost is mentioned.
So basically, they mentioned the cost of the entire car.
Because the car was almost totally damage.
The most expensive components were battery and motor.
Which are the core components of EV car.
After that, the insurance surveyor came.
He checked the car.
You won't believe, he gave a counter quotation
for only Rs 11 lakhs.
And said, repair it.
I asked the Mahindra people.
Will it be able to be repaired properly?
They denied on my face and said don't get it repaired.
Its condition is very bad.
And for them, this was their first major EV case.
Which had to be repaired.
So basically, an experiment was going to be done on my car.
And these insurance people are so smart.
That in their counter quotation,
In that, instead of XEV-9E, they had written XUV700.
Those who do not know the information of the car.
How will they be able to make the quotation correctly?
I kept fighting for 1.5 months.
I called everyone whom I could.
I took the contacts of the concerned authorities.
I took all the advantages of being a YouTuber.
I took out the contacts of ICICI.
I took out the contacts of Mahindra.
And after fighting for 1.5 months.
No one helped me.
Because in my mind, the biggest doubt was that
firstly this is an EV car.
Such an impactful accident has happened.
The whole thing is sensor based.
There is a battery in it.
I don't know what is the case of wiring in it.
I was so tensed.
I thought there could be any fault in the car while using it.
A few days ago, Trackin tech shared on Twitter.
About their XEV 9V.
That it stopped while driving.
You can read their case on Twitter.
I will put the link in the description.
And recently there has been a case of fire in a BE6.
Whose entire blame they have put on the tire.
And these are just 2 cases.
You can see a lot of such cases of BE6 and
XEV90 on the internet.
This is with new cars.
And still they are trying to give a repaired car.
And I gave the same argument to them.
But no, they refused it.
They said that it will be repaired.
Its cost is not going more than 10-11 lakhs.
They said that 11 lakhs is still on a higher side.
This car will be fixed in less than that.
So basically my declared value is around 29 lakhs.
So 70-75% of that is around 19 lakhs.
So if the cost of repair would have gone up to 19 lakhs.
Then they would have put it for total loss.
According to their policies.
Now the biggest role here is of the workshop people.
When the workshop people don't have
enough information about the car.
Then how will they fight with the insurance company.
You don't know what to put inside the car.
What is the cost of that thing.
Will you be able to counter them?
That it won't be fixed in 10-11 lakhs.
It can go to a total loss.
I told this in the Mahindra workshop.
But they said that no,
The insurance company is not agreeing.
You do as much expense as you get.
We will see.
This is what the insurance company said.
And from 1st or 2nd September.
Till 15th, 16th October.
After continuously fighting for 1.5 months.
There was no solution.
On 17th October, I said, you repair it.
And I wrote a big email that what are my concerns.
If something will be repaired,
then it should come in my hand.
So that I don't face a problem the next day.
Even Mahindra made me contact
the customer care manager here.
They assured me that they will give you a brand new car.
You won't even know that your car has been repaired.
And there will be no problem.
There will be no risk factor in it.
And the biggest promise.
You will get the car within a month.
You will get it before a month.
This happened around 17th-18th October.
That means I should have got it by mid-November.
I will tell you when I actually got it later.
And I specifically mentioned to the customer care manager.
That I will make a video on after-sales service.
So the better the service I get.
The better the feedback will go to the market.
So he mentioned that you don't take tension.
And the logic of keeping this video
factor is totally selfish.
I wanted a well repaired car
Because I didn't even drive 100 KMs,
A person who bought a car worth Rs 33 Lakhs.
Then approximately they took 3 months and
then called me for the first visit to check my car.
The final touch is pending but we have repaired your car.
And I took a very long checklist with me
Because obviously I am a tech YouTuber,
I wanted to see the shortcomings.
The speakers were not working,
The sensors were not working,
there were many issues in the body paint,
The wireless charger was not working.
These were the things that I was able to see
in the first visit in about an hour.
And I told them about 20-40 issues,
From the body to the internal parts
and told them that you will have to get it repaired.
Then they took 8-10 more days,
called me for another visit, Then I checked it,
Among all the shortcomings I told to them
and only a few of them were solved.
The rest of the problems were as it is,
I told them again that I am not enjoying the service,
You at least repair this,
You are calling me to show the car,
At least repair it properly.
Seriously, looking at the body paint, it looked like
it was painted from a roadside shop.
And after that, I didn't talk to them about the third visit,
I asked them to give me my car.
Approximately 3.5 months have passed,
Before that I have fought for 1.5 months,
I am only paying the EMI of the car since 5 months,
I haven't even driven the car,
I asked them to give me the car as it is.
And finally, on 29th January 2026, I get my car.
And now listen to the most interesting thing,
The story of Total Loss, Return to Invoice that I told you,
I directly asked them the cost,
how much did it cost to repair the car,
The cost of car repair was 18 lakh rupees.
They had said 10-11 lakhs, but neither the surveyor
had any experience about it,
Nor the workshop had any experience.
But who is suffering because of that? A consumer.
It could have easily gone for total Loss,
because there are still a lot of issues in this.
Because if this could have gone for Total loss,
I would have got a new car,
I would have been satisfied,
And I wouldn't have had to make this video.
Because as I said, it is not fun to share the pain,
Because whatever has happened,
Whatever you have seen about the accident, obviously,
You all must not be liking it.
And the excitement of the car on day 1,
When I bought the car,
After 5 months, it has become completely nil.
Now that car is not even 1% exciting for me.
And the repaired car that I got,
Which they were saying that they will make a
completely new car,
The condition of that car, just by looking at it physically,
it looks like a brand new car.
But there are a lot of shortcomings in the car.
First of all, I was looking at the wires, now you can see,
they have left exposed wires inside.
Now, the next day, whatever happens in the car,
They will blame the tires again.
And this is what I saw,
What type of connections are there inside,
What type of wiring they have left.
What can I say about this,
I am really scared while driving this car.
And look at the other things, look at the fitting
of the Harman's speaker on the left side,
it's not properly fit.
There are no screws in the glove box,
and the screws here are also missing.
There are body fill caps in many places in the car,
I can see them missing in many places,
I don't even know about the rest.
Even the USB-C port is not working for wired Android Auto.
And according to them, the car has been repaired,
The car has been completely dry cleaned.
But still, there are small glass particles in the car,
Even in the AC vents.
When I turned on the AC,
Small glass particles flew towards me.
And there are scratches everywhere,
this is how they have done fittings the car.
It looks like they have unprofessional, untrained mechanics
who doesn't even know how to use tools properly.
And I am telling you that the paint is so poor,
Even on areas which are newly painted,
They have done the touch-ups with brush strokes.
Roadside shops can do a better paintjob than them,
I got it done on my other car.
And when I checked the car twice,
there was no sound while driving.
Now, while driving, I can hear the sound,
Probably, it is the sound of the balancing rod.
And when you are buying a car after a long time,
You will hope that it will be fine.
On the screen, there is a battery low voltage error,
And on the driver's screen, there is a service sign.
This shows how trained their professional are.
I am feeling so scared thinking about the airbags
that they have fitted in the car.
I don't know if they will open in the future or not.
And the fitting alignment is not good, There are gaps.
Finishing is not good at all.
Obviously, after such a big accident,
If the car is being repaired.
Then these things are visible
But still, I have owned cars of other companies,
And I have seen the way they repair the car.
Mahindra's service is very bad.
And I have also experienced that.
You can search for information about
Mahindra service on the internet.
And among the issues I told you,
There were a lot of things that I told them in 2 visits
that this is the problem in this car.
And the thing about trained professionals and safety is that,
There are 3 seat belts on the back seat,
And there is a warning beep in this car.
Even if you don't put the seat belt on the
back seat, And it won't stop until you wear the belt.
There is no lock on one of the rear seat belt.
Just think about the quality check.
All they had to do was to repair the car and hand it over.
And these are the things that I have seen in 1 day.
It is not that they have refused to repair.
They told me to identify the problems
so that they can repair them
But what have you done in 3.5 months?
I have been paying EMI for the past 5 months.
I have given so much down payment.
And I am not driving the car,
Despite that, I am getting the car.
And still, I will come to you again to get the car repaired.
And the major concerns, Battery, Safety, Range of the car,
We will get to know while driving the car.
And seriously, I have a lot of doubts about this car.
If I face any problems in the future,
I will pin it in the comments of this video.
And while using the car, I got 1 more error.
Which is automatic emergency steering malfunction.
And because of this,
My headlight was turning on and off automatically.
And lane centering features were not working.
So those who have bought Mahindra's car,
Planned it, Booked it,
Read the comments,
You will get a lot of feedbacks from people.
And everyone, please share your
feedback in the comment section.
And share this video with those people.
So that the people could get aware about this.
I don't want this to happen to someone else.
And all these things will improve.
And yes, I will tell you again.
There is no problem in the car.
Safety wise, It is very good, It is features loaded.
Watch this video of mine.
I have explained all the features in detail.
And just see how excitedly I was reviewing that car.
And a special shoutout to Mr. Amish,
Mr. Praful and Mr. Shiv.
Who handled my case in the Mahindra workshop.
These people were very supportive.
They guided me in everything.
Whatever I said, Whatever the problems were,
They kept it very well at the management level.
And the fear will remain in the mind.
The case of BE6 in which the car caught fire,
That is still there in my mind.
And the other cases BE6 and XEV9E as well.
Because of that, I don't even have 1% expectation
from my repaired car.
That I can take it on the highway or
if it would run properly or not.
Now the fear or concern that is in my mind.
And the fact that I am roaming around with a repaired car.
Who will give an answer to this?
Insurance company.
Who didn't agree for the total loss.
Mahindra.
Who couldn't convince them for the total loss.
And I am surprised that this happened
with a YouTuber like me.
Who escalated the whole thing
and tried his best to get the task done.
Everyone knows whose car it is.
They even checked my review.
Even when I met some people from the team.
Then I got such a service.
So think about the condition of the common people.
And lastly, when all this was going on.
I didn't share it on social media.
I didn't want any negativity from me.
I was waiting.
Because the insurance company was not denying anything.
Mahindra was not denying anything.
I also had expectations that maybe I will get a good resolution.
But this is it.
What I shared with you.
You can like and share with people.
I will see you in the next video.
Till then, Bye.